[{"answer": "I did, actually.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "You thought I was going to hit you?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "I mean, you're very honest in the book, and commendably so.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "And I think it's not just me, it's for anyone, you know?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "As far as like the infidelity stuff, or --", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "I suppose the over riding question for me when I read it was, if you had your time again, would you do the same thing?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "Would you?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Yes, I think getting punched in the face by my dad was kind of like, whoa.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 106, "question": "Yes, but a proper punch is different, isn't it?", "qSentId": 105}, {"answer": "Well, I think it was probably learned behavior.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "Why was he so angry do you think?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Did he ever apologize to you for the hitting?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "You think he should?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Your big dream was to be a footballer.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "So, you know?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "When you think back to what you were doing then, do you recognize the man that you were then, a young man?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, totally.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "That they all run a mile (ph)?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "Well, I was juvenile.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "It's not easy, is it?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "Well, I never did it about the money.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Tell me how you got into this and realized I can make proper money at this?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "When you then get remarried to a porn star, Janine, who is abusive to you.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Anything else was secondary, you know?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "So you were drawn to it?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "When you first get together with Sandra, tell me about the early days.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "And like compared to like something that was chaos, you know, I kind of -- like wow, that's what I need to -- you know, that's the kind of person I need to be with, you know?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "I met her at the shop.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Where did you meet her?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "I think it was for me to a certain extent.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "Was it love at first sight you think?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "Yes, on a -- I'm like always the guy that like everyone wants to fight.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "Like a magnet for gossip?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "I think, you know, definitely the kids, and our like interests in, you know -- I don't know.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "What were the things that you had in common?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "AMES: I was pretty sure.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "You must have been sure then that this was the one for you?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "I don't think I ever had like a devil on my shoulder or something like that.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Given everything you've been through before, did you worry that although it all seemed so normal and nice and perfect for you, actually your character, your personality doesn't allow that kind of thing?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "Because the problem was with me.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "I think I've forgiven myself for what I've done.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "Yes, but I mean, do you hate yourself for doing that?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Has she forgiven you?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "I don't know -- well, I think for the -- everything that happens, I'm 100 percent to blame.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Can it be lonely to be that guy?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "Well, it just kind of takes me back to that day.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Well, what do you think when you hear that back?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "I think there were some suspicions, you know, which were right on her part.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "Did she have any inkling about what had been going on?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "How has she been about the book?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Nope.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "You don't talk to her at all?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "Then it's really nothing?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Several months ago.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "When was the last time you spoke to her?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Well, she told me before that she forgives me.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "How do you know she's forgiven you?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Do you think she understands you better than perhaps other people do?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "Your current partner?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "I think --", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Why do you think that is?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Have you changed?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "We're going to take another short break.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "If people -- I can be the villain, and she'll always be America's sweetheart, you know?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Well, I think this stuff is just trying to protect the kids, cause I'm a dad first and foremost.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "At its absolute worst, what were you going through?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "I couldn't care less, really.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Do you care now what they think?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Nope.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "Is he a Nazi?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "Have you ever had Nazi sympathies?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Nothing?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "It was a joke.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "Why -- why pose like that?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "You don't collect any Nazi memorabilia?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "I -- I think if you wanted to like point to anything and find some kind of like racism or anti-Semitism or anything, if you really looked at it long enough, you could build up whatever scenario you have.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "So you think that some people might -- might put that together with the picture, and get the wrong idea about you?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "Talked about her, or talked about --", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "If Sandra is watching this, which she might well be, how would you feel towards her listening to the way that you've talked about her?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "Garage we call it in England.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "What is -- well, Monster what?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "Garage.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "What do you call it?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "Garage actually sounds posher than I said it.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 585, "question": "Garage or Garage?", "qSentId": 584}, {"answer": "I think that's the first time I heard it called that.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 589, "question": "Is that what you call it?", "qSentId": 588}, {"answer": "I've never -- never saw him.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Are you -- are you allowed to see the child?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Since you left?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "Its been a year.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "So how long has that been now?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Have you tried to -- to get access?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "And its been denied to you?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "I don't know if grounds were given.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "On what grounds?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "They -- they do.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Do they ask you why they can't see their little brother?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "The -- the finality of the picture that you're painting suggests that Sandra -- I mean, you -- you may hope that she's forgiven you.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "You know, hey gone, splitting, separation, you know?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "Well, I kind of thought you deserved it, cause I couldn't get --", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "You take pride in that, don't you?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "Yes, the -- the first one was for punching a customer.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "Did you get freebies then?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "I -- I like them.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 690, "question": "You love your tattoos, don't you?", "qSentId": 689}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "Are -- are you engaged?", "qSentId": 698}, {"answer": "Well, she got me a ring made, and -- and gave it to me.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "Are -- are you married, cause you got a wedding ring on?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "When are you planning to get married?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 708, "question": "This is number four, right?", "qSentId": 707}, {"answer": "Do you think you may --", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 716, "question": "And you know, she's just awesome, you know?", "qSentId": 715}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 722, "question": "Do you believe you may have found true love?", "qSentId": 721}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 741, "question": "What's your point?", "qSentId": 740}, {"answer": "Movie star, actor.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 746, "question": "What does she do for a living?", "qSentId": 745}, {"answer": "An actor.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 749, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 748}, {"answer": "I -- I think you know, that whole -- that, you know, people that have to live in that world, and -- and --", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 753, "question": "You think it was an act?", "qSentId": 752}, {"answer": "Man -- 100 percent.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 755, "question": "Are you glad to be out of it?", "qSentId": 754}, {"answer": "It's just pretend.", "docId": "110513pmt", "aSentId": 764, "question": "Is that what you're saying?", "qSentId": 763}]